Guide to the Records of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1150 WAG.059
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XVI. 2019 Accretion, 1984-2002; 4.5 linear feet in 9 manuscript boxes
  - Local 1150 Elections, Laura Unger President's Files, Flyers and Leaflets, 1990-1993 (Box 84, Box 85)
  - Local 1150 Elections, Arbitration Files, 1990-1997 (Box 86)
  - Arbitration Files (RESTRICTED), 1991-1996 (Box 87, Box 89)
  - Arbitration Files, Notes, 1980-1998 (Box 88)